This is a trap, Chenyao.
Chenyao, Chenyao.
Li Qianqian.
What is his condition now?
He looks fine.
Lingze.
Chenyao.
Chenyao, are you okay? Chenyao!
I knew it would work.
What exactly are you trying to do?
What am I going to do now?
Come.
I'll show you what I'm doing now.
Lawyer Gu.
Xingcan.
Chen Yao.
Surprise, Chen Yao.
I went back
to December 1st with you.
You are the one
who gave me a new life.
Because of you,
I had the chance to defeat my father
and take back everything that belongs to me.
However,
you did cause me a lot of trouble.
Let Xingcan go and come at me.
Shut up.
Can't you see I'm talking?
To get rid of a demon like you,
I went to great lengths.
I set up such a big trap
just to eliminate all of you.
You really have been lying to us and acting all along.
It's obviously because you lied first.
I treated you so well before.
How dare you use me!
You deserve it.
You've done all kinds of evil.
You can't escape.
Is that so?
Isn't all this
Mr. Long's revenge?
Mr. Long did all this.
What does it have to do with me?
What do you mean?
I have to thank Chenyao.
It was him
who gave me this opportunity.
You two go over there and take a look.
Yes.
It's almost time.
I have to hurry and testify in court.
Chenyao.
Xingcan.
I'm coming to save you.
How truly touching.
Xingcan.
Don't say I didn't give you a chance.
You'd better hurry up.
Lingze, you bastard.
Xingcan.
I'm coming to save you.
Chenyao, are you okay?
Chenyao.
No.
No, Li Qianqian.
I know you're not a bad person.
Please let me go.
Qianqian.
I'm sorry.
I can't go back anymore.
Qianqian.
Come back.
Chenyao, wake up.
Don't leave me. I beg you.
I can't risk your body.
It's already come to this.
Almost.
Wait.
Don't go, okay?
Stay with me.
Thank you
for saving me time and time again.
Just like
a guardian angel.
Since you appeared when I was at my weakest
and let me rely on you,
the rest of my life should be the same.
Don't go, okay?
In the end.
Once again, you got hurt because of me.
Chenyao.
Maybe since our past life,
there has been too much regret and pain between us.
Meeting you in this life
has been, in my short life,
the happiest
and most dazzling moment.
But I beg you,
please live well
and wake up my father.
I hope in our next life,
we can meet again.
It's okay, Xingcan.
Let's go.
Chenyao.
Chenyao, what's wrong?
I'll go get some ice.
I don't have time.
Next,
I will wake up your father.
What are you doing?
Chenyao.
Chenyao, don't.
Don't.
Stop it.
Please, don't.
Xingcan.
You can stand on your own now.
You don't need me anymore.
No, I don't want to.
You said you would always stay by my side.
There must be another way.
There must be.
Chenyao.
Xingcan.
I always thought
I stayed by your side
to atone for my sins.
Only now do I realize
I... I did all this
because
I
love
you.
Chenyao.
Three, Huoyu.
Yao.
Chenyao.
Miss Gu, after you were thrown into the lake,
you were luckily rescued by a nearby fishing boat
and brought to safety.
Once you've recovered a bit,
please come to the police station to cooperate with our investigation
and describe in detail
how you were thrown into the water.
Okay.
Excuse me,
who brought me to the hospital?
It was the fisherman who brought you here.
The fisherman?
Male or female?
What did he look like?
Was he tall?
Did you see him carrying a pocket watch?
Sorry,
we don't know the details.
Thank you, then.
Hello, I'd like to pay the bill.
Hello.
Your bill has already been paid.
That person just left.
This is the phone number he left for you.
Already paid?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello.
This is...
Hello,
Chenyao.
I've already arrived.
Sorry, wrong person.
Psycho.
Everything
was just a dream after all.
But this dream was so real,
that I couldn't let it go for a long time.
After leaving the hospital,
I resumed my investigation into Lingze.
Having lost the protection of the person in my dreams,
I can only face all challenges alone.
Even though difficulties
weigh on me like mountains.
Whenever I feel inadequate
and think of giving up,
I always remember the words of that person in my dreams.
I made up my mind
to become someone who can handle difficulties independently.
This is also the promise
I made to that person.
To gather evidence,
I decided to put aside our past differences
and work with Mucheng again.
This time,
I acted as Mucheng's attorney.
Following the clues between Hao Zhenshi and Mucheng,
I dug deeper.
In the end,
with Xiaoya's help,
we successfully persuaded Li Qianqian.
With the sisters' seamless cooperation,
we finally gathered all the evidence.
We officially filed a lawsuit against Ling Ze and Ling Hengsheng.
Faced with conclusive evidence,
Ling Hengsheng and his son could no longer escape the law.
The court pronounces the following judgment:
The plaintiff's claims are established
and supported.
The defendant's related defenses are dismissed.
In the end,
we used legal means
and successfully sent them to prison.
A year's time
passed by
in a flash.
Now,
I have grown into
a mature
and experienced lawyer.
I also founded my own law firm.
I finally fulfilled my promise to that person.
This way,
my father in heaven
can rest in peace.
This
is the complete story
of my dream.
What caught your eye?
Little girl,
you have good taste.
A good friend of mine gave this to me.
He said to leave it with me
for someone destined to have it.
Where is this friend of yours?
Him?
Who knows where he went to enjoy himself.
Someone you can never forget,
is it possible to actually meet them?
Time,
is like a galaxy,
gathered by light-years.
But occasionally,
you can see it when you look up.
How about this?
I'll give it to you
as a memento of our meeting.
Is that okay?
Of course.
Take it.
Thank you.
I'll take it then.
No problem.
Dad,
don't worry.
I can stand on my own now.